

1987 February 1

Personal Profile

Web developer with troubleshooting skills and experience building web systems. Trained for teamwork under the agile SCRUM methodology. Self-taught and always willing to learn new development tools for my personal and professional growth.

Contact



+57-4126069697



chalds87@gmail.com



Caracas - Venezuela



chalds.github.io

Soft Skills

- Leadership.
- Analytical Thinking.
- Teamwork.
- Perspective.
- Solve Problems.
- Patience and Perseverance.
- Focus and productivity.
- Proactive.

Christian Lopez

Web Developer

Work Experience

Analyst Developer

Infoguia.com 2016 - Present

- Maintenance of the different existing systems in the company.
- Design and creation of new key internal systems for the operation of the company.
- Technical support to other team members.
- In charge of front end development of web applications using the VueJs Javascript framework for the consumption of APIs created with the PHP Laravel framework.

Education

Colegio Universitario Francisco de Miranda Computer Engineer | 2012 - 2016

Platzi Online Course Basic Programming Course | 2017

Platzi Online Course Introduction to PHP | 2017

Tech Stack

- JavaScript.
- PHP.
- VueJs.
- Visual Studio Code.
- Trello Board.
- GitHub Desktop.
- Microsoft Teams.
- Discord.

Idiomas

Spanish:

Native

English

Intermediate level



1987 Febrero 1

Perfil

Desarrollador web con habilidades para solucionar problemas y experiencia en creación de sistemas web. Capacitado para el trabajo en equipo bajo la metodología ágil SCRUM. Autodidacta y siempre dispuesto a aprender nuevas herramientas de desarrollo para mi crecimiento personal y profesional.

Contacto



+57-4126069697



chalds87@gmail.com



Caracas - Venezuela



chalds.github.io

Habilidades Blandas

- Liderazgo.
- Pensamiento analítico.
- Trabajo en equipo.
- Perspectiva.
- Resolución de problemas.
- Paciencia y perseverancia.
- Enfoque y productividad.
- Proactivo.

Christian Lopez

Desarrollador Web

Experiencia laboral

Analista Programador

Infoguia.com 2016 - Actualidad

- Mantenimiento de los diferentes sistemas existentes en la empresa.
- Diseño y creación de nuevos sistemas internos clave para el funcionamiento de la empresa.
- Apoyo técnico a otros miembros del equipo.
- Encargado del desarrollo Front End de aplicaciones web usando el framework de Javascript VueJs para el consumo de APIs creadas con el framework de PHP Laravel.

Datos académicos

Colegio Universitario Francisco de Miranda Ingeniero Informática | 2012 - 2016

Curso Online Platzi Curso de Programación Básica | 2017

Curso Online Platzi Introducción a PHP | 2017

Herramientas Técnicas

- JavaScript.
- PHP.
- VueJs.
- Visual Studio Code.
- Trello Board.
- GitHub Desktop.
- Microsoft Teams.
- Discord.

Idiomas

Español: Nativo.

Inglés: Nivel medio.